

Guilherme Emilio Guain Peixinho Front-end Developer

- ⊠ guilherme.guain@gmail.com
- © São Paulo, SP Brazil
- ⋒ guilhermeguain.com.br

I have been working with web development since 2012, when I started in a communication agency creating websites in Wordpress. After 8 years of experience in this technology, I started a specialization in React.js. In addition, I also follow Clean Code and SOLID principles, respecting technical SEO practices with a focus on problem solving.





TECHS & TOOLS

PRIMARY: React.js, TypeScript, Next.js, ESLint, Git, Tailwind CSS and Postman.

SECONDARY: PHP, Node.js, MySQL, WordPress, AMP, GraphQL, Sass and Gulp.

DESIGN: Figma, Photoshop e Illustrator.

LANGUAGES

PORTUGUESE: Native ENGLISH: Intermediate

Experience

Toxicologia Pardini

08/2018 - present Full-stack Developer











Reference company in toxicology testing where I act as a full-stack developer responsible for the development and maintenance of the site. Among the main activities are: on-page SEO optimization, implementation of new features, bug fixes and integrations with internal systems, CRM and ERP.

Amo Promo

Front-end Developer 01/2023 - 04/2024









With the aim of promoting unforgettable experiences, I work on the planning and development of web and mobile solutions using the latest technologies.

Health Protection

09/2020 - 10/2022 Front-end Developer









The project was developed using Next.js with TypeScript and tools such as the Context API, Axios, Tailwind CSS, Chakra UI, ESLint, and React Query. For content management, we used Sanity CMS. My activities involved front-end development, API integration, component and page creation, maintenance and bug fixing, and also continuous deployment with Netlify and Vercel.

Education

React.js - Ignite	HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript and Bootstrap	11/2017 - 02/2018
ROCKETSEAT	ALURA	Online
GoStack - Node.js, React.js and React Native ROCKETSEAT	Programming logic and PHP	10/2012 - 06/2014 São Paulo, SP
Nanodegree Front-end Web Developer	Graphic Design Technician	05/2012 - 05/2013
UDACITY	ALPHA CHANNEL	São Paulo, SP